var init = { "questions": [ {"question": "What is the function of the Clipboard?", "answers": ["It is a hold area in which to place information for use between different software programs.","It is an online area where users post questions.","It is an area from which the user can print.","It is an area that a browser uses to store recently visited web pages."], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "The function of this key is to place a copy of the screen on the clipboard.", "answers": ["Copy key","Alt key		","F12 key","Print Screen key"], "correctAnswer": 4},{"question": "What is the keyboard shortcut for the copy command?", "answers": ["CTRL Copy	","CTRL C","CTRL Insert","CTRL V"], "correctAnswer": 2},{"question": "What is the keyboard shortcut for the paste command?", "answers": ["CTRL Copy","CTRL C","CTRL Insert","CTRL V "], "correctAnswer": 4},{"question": "When using the copy command, before the paste command is applied, the text/graphic chosen is temporarily placed on the", "answers": ["Clipboard","Holding station","Format merge","Converter"], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "To print a picture of the computer screen, you must first hit the Print Screen button on the keyboard and then", "answers": ["execute the Copy command in a spreadsheet program.","execute the Put command in a Paint program.","execute the Paste command in any word processing program.","click Print in any program."], "correctAnswer": 3},{"question": "Which of the following commands places a copy of a selected object on the Clipboard?", "answers": ["Paste	","Select All	","Copy ","Edit "], "correctAnswer": 3},{"question": "Which of the following commands takes a copy of an item on the Clipboard and places it where the cursor is located in a document?", "answers": ["Cut","Paste	","Put","Redo"], "correctAnswer": 2},{"question": "Once something is copied on the Clipboard, it can be pasted", "answers": ["multiple times, until something else is placed on the Clipboard","up to five times","only one time ","three times and then it is deleted"], "correctAnswer": 1},{"question": "The full ____________ of a file indicates the drive, all the subdirectories, and the file name.", "answers": ["Path name","Folder name	","File name","Driver name "], "correctAnswer": 1}]};